{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Attic \u0026 Whole House Fan Installers","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40245/":{"taskOID":40245,"originalTaskOID":40245,"setID":552,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":3041,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Attic Fan Wanted","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of fan(s) do you want? (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6957,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Whole house ventilation fan","answerDisplayText":"Whole house ventilation fan","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5408,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Roof mounted attic fan","answerDisplayText":"Roof mounted attic fan","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2701,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Gable vent mounted","answerDisplayText":"Gable vent mounted","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3109,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Humidistat controlled","answerDisplayText":"Humidistat controlled","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5877,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Solar powered","answerDisplayText":"Solar powered","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5729,"questionDisplayText":"Features","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What fan features interest you? (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1928,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Direct drive","answerDisplayText":"Direct drive","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1018,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Belt driven","answerDisplayText":"Belt driven","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6556,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Two speed","answerDisplayText":"Two speed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6661,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Variable speed","answerDisplayText":"Variable speed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6324,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Thermostatically controlled","answerDisplayText":"Thermostatically controlled","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6378,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Timer","answerDisplayText":"Timer","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5143,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Remote control","answerDisplayText":"Remote control","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5877,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Solar powered","answerDisplayText":"Solar powered","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":40001,"questionDisplayText":"Materials Provided by Homeowner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Will you provide materials for this request?","shortQuestionText":"Homeowner to provide materials?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":3041,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Attic Fan Wanted","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of fan(s) do you want? (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6957,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Whole house ventilation fan","answerDisplayText":"Whole house ventilation fan","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5408,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Roof mounted attic fan","answerDisplayText":"Roof mounted attic fan","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2701,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Gable vent mounted","answerDisplayText":"Gable vent mounted","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3109,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Humidistat controlled","answerDisplayText":"Humidistat controlled","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5877,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Solar powered","answerDisplayText":"Solar powered","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":6957,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Whole house ventilation fan","answerDisplayText":"Whole house ventilation fan","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5408,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Roof mounted attic fan","answerDisplayText":"Roof mounted attic fan","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2701,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Gable vent mounted","answerDisplayText":"Gable vent mounted","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3109,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Humidistat controlled","answerDisplayText":"Humidistat controlled","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5877,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Solar powered","answerDisplayText":"Solar powered","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5729,"questionDisplayText":"Features","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What fan features interest you? (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1928,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Direct drive","answerDisplayText":"Direct drive","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1018,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Belt driven","answerDisplayText":"Belt driven","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6556,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Two speed","answerDisplayText":"Two speed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6661,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Variable speed","answerDisplayText":"Variable speed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6324,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Thermostatically controlled","answerDisplayText":"Thermostatically controlled","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6378,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Timer","answerDisplayText":"Timer","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5143,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Remote control","answerDisplayText":"Remote control","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5877,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Solar powered","answerDisplayText":"Solar powered","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":1928,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Direct drive","answerDisplayText":"Direct drive","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1018,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Belt driven","answerDisplayText":"Belt driven","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6556,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Two speed","answerDisplayText":"Two speed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6661,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Variable speed","answerDisplayText":"Variable speed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6324,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Thermostatically controlled","answerDisplayText":"Thermostatically controlled","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6378,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Timer","answerDisplayText":"Timer","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5143,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Remote control","answerDisplayText":"Remote control","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5877,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Solar powered","answerDisplayText":"Solar powered","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":40001,"questionDisplayText":"Materials Provided by Homeowner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Will you provide materials for this request?","shortQuestionText":"Homeowner to provide materials?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/40245/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40245,"taskName":"Attic or Whole House Fan - Install","taskDescription":"Install an Attic or Whole House Fan","xmTaskDescriptor":"Attic \u0026 Whole House Fan Installers","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":14,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Attic Insulation Replacement Fan Whole","textMessagingName":"Install Attic Fan","rolloverLongDesc":"These fans exhaust air through a hole in the roof, through an existing gable (end wall) vent or through a gable opening created for this purpose. Attic fans prevent build-up of heat \u0026/or moisture in the attic. This person can handle the wiring, mounting \u0026 any necessary hole cutting.","rolloverShortDesc":"Includes electrical work \u0026 mounting.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Install an Attic or Whole House Fan.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Attic Fan Installation \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Install Whole House Fan","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":25,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Attic Fan Install","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Attic or Whole House Fan - Install","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Attic or Whole House Fan Installation Project","urlName":"Attic-or-Whole-House-Fan-Install","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Attic \u0026 Whole House Fan Installers - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Cost \u0026 Reviews","searchKeywords":"Attic,Insulation,Replacement,Fan,Whole,conditioning,solar,exhaust,air","emcCategoryOid":-12029,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":552,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false}}